<resources language="en">
  <group>Group</group>
  <group_description>You see all group members on a single map, they also see you when you have enabled the tracking.<br />
You can plan a trip with the whole group: place in group points and tracks for easy simultaneous navigation of multiple devices.</group_description>
  <group_problem>It is impossible to get access to the group</group_problem>
  <group_add>Create group</group_add>
  <group_find>Find group</group_find>
  <group_no_latlon>Do not set the initial coordinates of the group</group_no_latlon>
  <activity>Last activity</activity>
  <join_group>Join group</join_group>
  <leave_group>Leave group</leave_group>
  <join_note>Please log in to join the group through the website</join_note>
  <join_note_byid>Without authorization, you can join the group via any of our app by ID</join_note_byid>
  <you_in_group>Are you in the group</you_in_group>
  <you_joined>You joined</you_joined>
  <b1t>Create a group</b1t>
  <b1d>The group is a great way of sharing your location</b1d>
  <b2t>Join the group</b2t>
  <b2d1>In mobile application you are using, look for "Join group" in the ID field enter U or ID or URL of the group (no registration required)</b2d1>
  <b2d2>If you have registered, you can join the group via the website</b2d2>
  <bd1t>Map</bd1t>
  <bd1d>You can add to the group map gpx-tracks or waypoints, they will be downloaded to all group members automatically</bd1d>
  <bd2t>Control</bd2t>
  <bd2d>If the group type allows allows it, you can control the monitoring on the devices in the group. All at once or individually.</bd2d>
  <bd3t>Geofence</bd3t>
  <bd3d>You can add a map of the area, at the entrance and exit system will notify the members of the group, and you can also assign additional scripts</bd3d>
  <bd4t>Scenario</bd4t>
  <bd4d>The ability to specify different actions in the group are bound to different events: such as time, connect to a specific Wifi-network or enter to a geofence</bd4d>
  <tips>Short instruction</tips>
  <tips1>Suppose you want to monitor for 5 people</tips1>
  <tips2>Download for all devices OsMoDroid</tips2>
  <tips3>One person registers and creates a group (via the app or website)</tips3>
  <tips4>The creator of the group passes to other people group ID, and they come into it</tips4>
  <tips5>Ready! Now, when need be, to enable monitoring!</tips5>
  <tips6>Learn the answers to frequently asked questions</tips6>
  <group_is_frozen>Group is frozen by owner</group_is_frozen>
  <group_private_warn>Do not distribute this ID without the consent of the members of the group</group_private_warn>
  <group_restricted>Participants in this group, only administrators can add</group_private_warn>
  <users_active>Active</users_active>
  <users_viewers>Audience</users_viewers>
</resources>