<resources language="en">
  <group>Group</group>
  <group_description>You see all group members on a single map, they also see you when you have enabled the tracking.<br />
You can plan a trip with the whole group: place in group points and tracks for easy simultaneous navigation of multiple devices.</group_description>
  <group_problem>It is impossible to get access to the group</group_problem>
  <with_osmodroid>Monitor via OsMoDroid</with_osmodroid>
  <with_osmodroid_description>Our official client uses the widest range of the service's features</with_osmodroid_description>
  <with_osmand>Use OsmAnd</with_osmand>
  <with_osmand_description>OsmAnd is a powerful navigation program with a dedicated plugin for OsMo. Use it to communicate with other users, share tracks and use navigation functions.</with_osmand_description>
  <with_website>Access via the website</with_website>
  <with_website_description>This is an easy and a simple way to view, monitor and manage groups conveniently via any web browser</with_website_description>
  <group_add>Create group</group_add>
  <group_find>Find group</group_find>
  <group_no_latlon>Do not set the initial coordinates of the group</group_no_latlon>
  <activity>Last activity</activity>
  <join_group>Join group</join_group>
  <join_note>Please log in to join the group through the website</join_note>
  <join_note_byid>Without authorization, you can join the group via any of our app by ID</join_note_byid>
  <you_in_group>Are you in the group</you_in_group>
  <you_joined>You joined</you_joined>
  <b1t>You need to see each other? Create a group!</b1t>
  <b1d>Group specially created in order to be aware of who is where</b1d>
  <b2t>Does your community already have a group? Join!</b2t>
  <b2d1>In mobile application you are using, look for "Join group" in the ID field enter U or ID or URL of the group (no registration required)</b2d1>
  <b2d2>If you have registered, you can join the group via the website</b2d2>
  <b3t>Plan your trip</b3t>
  <b3d>You can add gpx tracks or waypoints - they will be available to all members of the group automatically even after disconnecting it connection</b3d>
  <tips>Short instruction</tips>
  <tips1>Suppose you want to monitor for 5 people</tips1>
  <tips2>Download for all devices OsMoDroid</tips2>
  <tips3>One person registers and creates a group (via the app or website)</tips3>
  <tips4>The creator of the group passes to other people group ID, and they come into it</tips4>
  <group_is_frozen>Group is frozen by owner</group_is_frozen>
  <group_private_warn>Do not distribute this ID without the consent of the members of the group</group_private_warn>
</resources>