<resources language="en">
  <index_title_1>OpenStreetMap Monitoring</index_title_1>
  <index_desc_1>Mobile GPS-monitoring allows you to easily share geo-data: coordinates, points, tracks</index_desc_1>
  <index_title_2>The best solution for mobile GPS monitoring</index_title_2>
  <index_desc_2>Creating a group of friends in OsMo, you'll be able to quickly find each other. It is very comfortable in the woods and in the city!</index_desc_2>
  <index_title_3>Types of monitoring</index_title_3>
  <index_title_3_1>With the organization</index_title_3_1>
  <index_title_3_2>Family</index_title_3_2>
  <index_title_3_3>During the journey</index_title_3_3>
  <index_title_3_4>Securely</index_title_3_4>
  <index_desc_3_1>Sled dog race, or a taxi company - our solution is very flexible</index_desc_3_1>
  <index_desc_3_2>Why the child stayed in school? Accurate information with minimal power consumption</index_desc_3_2>
  <index_desc_3_3>Share your experiences or organize a convoy of cars on the track. Drive through the countryside or tour around the world :)</index_desc_3_3>
  <index_desc_3_4>We care about the peace of mind your loved ones every day for more than 2 years</index_desc_3_4>
  <index_title_4>Download our app right now:</index_title_4>
  <index_desc_4>And watch through the website</index_desc_4>
  
  <personal>Personal</personal>
  <personal_description>You can share your location with anyone's quick, easy and anonymously using disposable or permanent link received in the application</personal_description>
  <group>Groups</group>
  <group_description>Group monitoring allows all group members to share locations and points of interest in real time. The administrator can place additional routes and create geofences. In groups, have a chat and notification system. Use groups for clubs, families, travel, competitions or other events.</group_description>
  <family>Family</family>
  <family_description>Special groups for use every day. You will always know where your husband and children. In addition to standard functions, you will always know the battery level of the devices of the family members to have the ability to control monitoring other family member and the signal SOS.</family_description>
  <journey>Trip/Travel</journey>
  <journey_description>If you went on a long journey, you'll appreciate this type of groups. Specify the start and end dates of your trip and the system will automatically publish your way every day, so the observer can see the entire path of your journey online.</journey_description>
  <contest>Contest</contest>
  <contest_description>Group created specifically for the various events related to navigation.</contest_description>
  <event>Event</event>
  <event_description>Group with automatic control of start of monitoring for the period of the action.</event_description>
</resources>
