<resources language="en">
    <index_title>OsMo — Tracker</index_title>
    <index_desc>Our service helps you record your trips, workouts and walks every day for further analysis.
        The OsMoDroid app records a high-precision track with a frequency of 1 Hz online, thereby capturing the dynamics of your path as accurately as possible.
        Thanks to online trip recording, you can share your location with the whole world or specific people.
    </index_desc>

    <menu_1>Begin</menu_1>
    <menu_2>Features</menu_2>
    <menu_3>Review</menu_3>
    <menu_4>Help</menu_4>


    <feature>Key features</feature>

    <feature1_title>Trip recording</feature1_title>
    <feature1_description>Install the app, click "Run". That's all it takes to start recording your trip and showing your location on a temporary link with the highest possible accuracy.</feature1_description>

    <feature2_title>Permanent</feature2_title>
    <feature2_description>Create a personal link in the app and you can be watched daily by a fixed link. You can close the link with a password or publish it as a frame inside your site</feature2_description>

    <feature3_title>Group</feature3_title>
    <feature3_description>Create a group in one minute and invite members of your community. When participants are to start monitoring, their location would be visible to all who have access to the group via the mobile app and the website. Ideal for public group bike rides or car rides</feature3_description>

    <feature4_title>Family</feature4_title>
    <feature4_description>Create a special "Family" group and invite your relatives to join it. All family members will see each other's location, constantly, through apps or a website with minimal power consumption and no need to turn on the tracker manually</feature4_description>


    <reviews>Reviews (from Play Store)</reviews>

    <review1_author>Grab Guh</review1_author>
    <review1_profession>Driver</review1_profession>
    <review1_text>Excellent for everyone who work with Grab, Uber, Go-Car or any taxi/mobile service. Especially when you have a group and need to monitor everyone's position. Also good for monitoring family location.</review1_text>

    <review2_author>Kiti Thengtrirat</review2_author>
    <review2_profession>Father</review2_profession>
    <review2_text>Great app to track your child give them a cell phone and you don't worry much.  Dangerous app to give to your wife, you can't go any where...love it, live it ... especially when traffic jam and you wait for someone back home.</review2_text>

    <review3_author>Randy Schnedler</review3_author>
    <review3_profession>User</review3_profession>
    <review3_text>No registration required to use it, though registration does give you even more power. Great stuff, frequent updates. Just keeps getting better! Thank you, dev!</review3_text>

    <support>If you have any questions, please contact us</support>
</resources>