<resources language="en">
    
  <personal>Monitoring</personal>
  <personal_description>Shows your current location</personal_description>
  
  <b1t>Easy and simple</b1t>
  <b1d>By installing the application working with OsMo, share your location easily</b1d>
  
  <b2t>Share the trip</b2t>
  <b2d>When you start sending coordinates, generated links of the form https://osmo.mobi/s/**_***_** it is valid until you complete the trip</b2d>
  
  <b3t>Permalink</b3t>
  <b3d>If you need to give permanent access to your location, you can create a Permalink, it will always show your location. The current or saved if you shut down sending coordinates. The link works forever until it is deleted.</b3d>
  
  <good_to_know>Good to know</good_to_know>
  <gtk0>Every time you start and stop monitoring in our system submitted in a separate "trip"</gtk0>
  <gtk1>At the same time not one authorized device or one account can have only one trip</gtk1>
  <gtk2>After the trip started, for 24 hours, must be sent at least one coordinate, otherwise it is deemed null and will be removed</gtk2>
  <gtk3>The maximum number of points per trip ~200 000, then it can be forcibly terminated</gtk3>
  <gtk4>If not authorized, the device does not send coordinates within 12 hours, the trip is automatically terminated</gtk4>
  <gtk5>If the account is not received coordinate within 36 hours, the trip is automatically terminated</gtk5>
  <gtk6>If the majority of the points sent in the last 24 hours will be with zero speed - the drive is considered useless, and the device can be locked</gtk6>
  
  <session_ended>The trip has already ended</session_ended>
  <session_ended_description>To continue to observe this unit you can ask for a link to a new session, the permanent link or log in with a user in one group</session_ended_description>
  
  <personal_not_found>This link leads nowhere</personal_not_found>
  <personal_not_found_description>You may ask whoever you sent it new</personal_not_found_description>
  
</resources>