<resources language="en">
    
  <personal>Monitoring</personal>
  <personal_description>Shows your current location</personal_description>
  
  <b1t>Easy and simple</b1t>
  <b1d>By installing the application working with OsMo, share your location easily</b1d>
  
  <b2t>Share the trip</b2t>
  <b2d>When you start sending coordinates, generated links of the form https://osmo.mobi/s/**_***_** it is valid until you complete the trip</b2d>
  
  <b3t>Permalink</b3t>
  <b3d>If you need to give permanent access to your location you can create a Permalink. The link will always show your location (current or saved). Please note that we also see your online status.</b3d>
  
  <good_to_know>Good to know</good_to_know>
  <gtk0>Every time you start and stop monitoring creates a "trip", which is then stored in history</gtk0>
  <gtk1>At the same time not one authorized device or one account can have only one trip</gtk1>
  <gtk2>Once travel has commenced, within 6 hours, should be sent at least one coordinate, otherwise it is considered empty and will be removed</gtk2>
  <gtk3>The maximum number of sent coordinate for the trip ~25 000, after exceeding the limit point it may be forcibly terminated</gtk3>
  <gtk4>If you are not an authorized device does not send coordinates within a few hours, the trip will automatically end</gtk4>
  <gtk5>If the account is not received coordinate within 8 hours, the trip will automatically end</gtk5>
  <gtk6>If the majority of the points sent in the last 24 hours, with zero speed - the drive is considered useless and will not be saved</gtk6>
  
  <session_ended>Trip completed</session_ended>
  <session_ended_description>To continue monitoring this person, you can ask them for a new link, a permanent link, add them to friends, or create a group</session_ended_description>
  
  <personal_not_found>This link leads nowhere</personal_not_found>
  <personal_not_found_description>You may ask whoever you sent it new</personal_not_found_description>
  
</resources>